# **DOMINIK BURSY**

**Economics Graduate** 

German Citizen

**\** +49 173 3686 203

4 August 1993, Munich

dominik.bursy@icloud.com

Andréestr. 8, 80634 Munich

github.com/dbursy

# ABOUT ME -

I am an economics graduate with research interests in Environmental & Development Economics and Political Economy. I am interested in how climate, natural disasters and social issues affect regional economic and human development. This includes political opinion formation and the determinants of individual and collective decision making, as well as the application of modern methods for causal inference and spatial statistics.

#### **EDUCATION** -

## **Master of Science, Economics**

10/2020 - 03/2023

Ludwig-Maximilians-Universität, LMU Munich

Munich, Germany

Thesis: Climate Change Risk and Economic Activity - Urban Implications to Wildfire Exposure

#### Study Abroad, Erasmus Exchange Program

10/2020 - 02/2021

ENSAE Paris, Institut Polytechnique de Paris

Paris, France

Specialization: Economics of Competition

## **Bachelor of Science, Economics**

10/2016 - 09/2019

Ludwig-Maximilians-Universität, LMU Munich

Munich, Germany

Thesis: Erroneous Strategic Thinking in Disclosure Games

# Study Abroad, Erasmus Exchange Program

09/2018 - 03/2019

University of Warwick

Warwick, UK

Specialization: Microeconomics and Strategic Interaction

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Data Expert in Data Intelligence

11/2022 - 03/2024

Allianz SE | Group Data & Al

Munich, Germany

- Focus: Business Data Improvement
- · Strategic planning, execution and delivery of data analytics and AI solutions
- · Collaboration with technical and business stakeholders to define project goals and deliverables

#### **Professional Certificate: Machine Learning Engineer**

03/2023 - 08/2023

Université Paris 1 Panthéon-Sorbonne, DataScientest

Paris, France

· Deployment of Machine Learning models following MLOps principles like CI/CD practices

# **Working Student in Data Intelligence**

05/2021 - 10/2022

Allianz SE | Group Data & Al

Munich, Germany

- Focus: External Data & Data Value Extraction
- · Consolidation of external data sources across the company landscape
- · Generation of a geospatial dataset using the Google Places API to improve risk classification

# **Vocational Training as a Marketing Communications Specialist**

09/2011 - 01/2014

Getmobile GmbH

Munich, Germany

- · Focus: Digital marketing and web design
- · Market and competitor analysis using GfK's Reports
- · Monitoring of advertising campaigns using Google Analytics

#### RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

#### Research Assistant, Ref.: Prof. Kai A. Konrad

06/2019 - 09/2020

Econlab, Max Planck Institute for Tax Law and Public Finance

Munich, Germany

- · Organizing and assisting social science experiments
- · Recruiting participants and managing the database

# Research Assistant, Ref.: Prof. Sascha O. Becker

10/2018 - 08/2019

Department of Economics, University of Warwick

Warwick, UK

- Digitizing data on construction activities and taxation in Germany
- · Researching German military activity in Poland during World War II

#### Student Assistant, Ref.: Dr. Alexandra Hauser

07/2017 - 09/2018

Center for Leadership and People Management, LMU Munich

Munich, Germany

- Requirement planning to support the P2P-Mentoring Program
- Managing the homepage (creating articles, adding features, etc.)

#### TEACHING EXPERIENCE -

#### Student Tutorial for Undergraduates: Macroeconomics 2

04/2021 - 07/2021

Department of Economics, LMU Munich

Munich, Germany

- · Introduction to Neoclassical Growth Theory based on the Solow-Swan Growth Model
- · Review of comparative statics and discussion of environmental extensions and their implications

# Student Tutorial for Undergraduates: Econometrics 2 (R)

07/2017 - 09/2018

Department of Economics, LMU Munich

Munich, Germany

- · Introduction to the statistical software R (RStudio)
- · Review of methods for the analysis of cross-sectional and panel data

# **Student Tutorial for Undergraduates: Pre-Course Mathematics**

10/2019

Department of Economics, LMU Munich

Munich, Germany

• Review of basic math concepts (Power and Matrix Calculation)

#### MISCELLANEOUS

Programming Python, Stata, R (RStudio), SQL, Stata, Matlab, LaTeX, HTML & CSS, Git, z-Tree/oTree, Spark,

Docker, Kubernetes

Languages German (native), English (proficient), French (basic)